<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><TranslationRequest><ID>480</ID><JobName>TA_DRUPAL_5862_B2B_T4B_480_AOB</JobName><RequestedLangs><Lang>da_DK</Lang><Lang>it_IT</Lang><Lang>tr_TR</Lang><Lang>no_NO</Lang><Lang>ko_KR</Lang><Lang>es_LX</Lang><Lang>id_ID</Lang><Lang>th_TH</Lang><Lang>de_DE</Lang><Lang>en_GB</Lang><Lang>el_GR</Lang><Lang>zh_TW</Lang><Lang>pt_BR</Lang><Lang>pl_PL</Lang><Lang>sv_SE</Lang><Lang>fr_FR</Lang><Lang>ru_RU</Lang><Lang>es_ES</Lang><Lang>ja_JP</Lang><Lang>nl_NL</Lang></RequestedLangs><Comments><Comment>This (unpublished) article just needs a few sentences re-translated due to a factual error. First two sentences in the "Quantity and recency of reviews": Prior to the review collection partnership with TripAdvisor, Shangri-La properties were averaging 6 reviews each month. Since the partnership began in July 2013, that average has increased 250% to 21 reviews per property per month. Please do NOT re-translate the rest of the piece. Everything else is good. Thanks!;</Comment><Comment>{Content Template: 1};</Comment><Comment>Update of these previous languages/requests: {"en-GB":450,"zh-hant":450,"da":450,"nl":450,"fr":450,"de":450,"el":450,"id":450,"it":450,"ja":450,"ko":450,"es-latam":450,"nb":450,"pl":450,"pt-br":450,"ru":450,"es":450,"sv":450,"th":450,"tr":450}.;</Comment></Comments><Translations><Translation><KeyName>title_field.en.0.value</KeyName><ID>557123</ID><EnglishMaster>Shangri-La’s heavenly approach to review collection</EnglishMaster></Translation><Translation><KeyName>body.en.0.value</KeyName><ID>557124</ID><EnglishMaster>&lt;p&gt;Like their fictional namesake, Shangri-La hotels are known as paradises on earth. But unlike the isolated and mystical locale from the novel Lost Horizon, each Shangri-La property is welcoming and luxurious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since the partnership began, the number of reviews collected has increased 250%.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And enticing guests requires a strong online presence, which is why Shangri-La Hotels and Resorts partnered with TripAdvisor to collect reviews. By teaming up with the world’s largest travel site, the leading luxury hotel group in Asia Pacific has seen great success. And that’s quite the accomplishment, considering the many positive reviews Shangri-La already gets due to their high standards of service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Top level results&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far, the results have been very positive for Shangri-La properties around the world. After just one year, the review collection partnership has:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Driven nearly 30% of review volume&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Led to reviews with a 3.6% higher average rating, by prompting more guests who may not have written a review to share their positive experience&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Rocketed 5 additional properties into the top 5% of their market on TripAdvisor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;How the partnership works&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The partnership drives additional reviews with little extra effort by easily integrating a TripAdvisor review form into Shangri-La guest satisfaction surveys. Guests have the option of completing a review at the end of the survey, which is then automatically provided to TripAdvisor for moderation and publication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a result of this simple yet effective partnership, Shangri-La has seen a boost in the three key factors that influence a property’s popularity on TripAdvisor: quantity, recency and quality of reviews.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Quantity and recency of reviews&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prior to the review collection partnership with TripAdvisor, Shangri-La properties were averaging 6 reviews each month. Since the partnership began in July 2013, that average has increased 250% to 21 reviews per property per month. All together, the review collection partnership has driven an average of 534 out of 1930 reviews per month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Quality of reviews&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to providing a steady flow of new reviews, the review form integration has also shown to provide reviews with a higher rating. Reviews collected in partnership average a 4.56 rating out of 5, compared to an average rating of 4.40 for reviews from other sources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Newfound popularity&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to the increase in reviews and ratings, 5 additional Shangri-La properties have jumped into the top 5% of their market. &amp;nbsp;In particular, the &lt;a href="http://www.tripadvisor.com/Hotel_Review-g293974-d4176982-Reviews-Shangri_La_Bosphorus_Istanbul-Istanbul.html" target="_blank"&gt;Shangri-La Bosphorus&lt;/a&gt; in Istanbul has climbed from 332 of 820 properties to 47 of 898&amp;nbsp;properties. And the &lt;a href="http://www.tripadvisor.com/Hotel_Review-g308272-d4089880-Reviews-Jing_An_Shangri_La_West_Shanghai-Shanghai.html" target="_blank"&gt;Jing An Shangri-La&lt;/a&gt; in West Shanghai has risen from 227 of 3,111 properties to 36 of 3,717 properties. In short, the review collection partnership has helped these relatively new properties boost their number of reviews, leading to a dramatic rise in TripAdvisor ranking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Better ranking means more page views&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a result of this increased popularity, Shangri-La properties have seen a dramatic increase in page views on TripAdvisor. In June, 2014 engagement for Shangri-La properties on TripAdvisor jumped 52%, nearly double the average growth for properties around the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By simply integrating a TripAdvisor review form into their existing guest satisfaction survey, Shangri-La hotels and resorts have dramatically enhanced their presence on the world’s largest travel site. Reviews are up, ratings are up and as a result, Shangri-La properties are catching the attention of more travelers seeking a slice of “paradise on earth”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To learn more about forming a review collection partnership with TripAdvisor for your properties, contact &lt;a href="mailto:partnerships@tripadvisor.com?subject=Re%3A%20Shangri-La%20review%20collection%20partnership" target="_blank"&gt;partnerships@tripadvisor.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</EnglishMaster></Translation><Translation><KeyName>field_introduction.en.0.value</KeyName><ID>557125</ID><EnglishMaster>Asia Pacific’s leading luxury hotel group increases reviews, ratings and rankings with TripAdvisor review collection partnership.</EnglishMaster></Translation></Translations><Register>B2B</Register><Cost>T4B</Cost></TranslationRequest>